<tutorial>
<title>Touch Events</title>
<text>Along with the onBoundaryCollision Event you have seen, you will also be able to use the onTouch Event.

Similar to the onBoundaryCollision, the onTouch Event's syntax looks like:

sub onTouch with x,y
	[list of commands]
return

If you are not familiar with sub-routines with parameters, this is the format of what they look like.
With x,y means that there are two parameters being passed into the onTouch Event. In this case, the x and y location on the screen that is being touched.

Although, this will be a useful tool in programming your BOT, do not rely the onTouch Event as some BOT's will be able to jam your BOT's radar, causing it to lose
this onTouch capability.
</text>
<stage>
<hint>Begin by setting a global variable _a equal to 0.
Write the same while loop to move you BOT as before, but set the angle parameter to be the global variable you created.

Your Code should look like this:
let _a = 0
while 1 do
	call bot_move(_a, 5)
loop
</hint>
<answer>let _a = 0
while 1 do
	call bot_move(_a, 5)
loop</answer>
</stage>
<stage>
<hint>Goal: Move the BOT in the direction of where you Touch.
To do this you must set up the onTouch with x,y Event Routine.

This Event looks like:

sub onTouch with x,y
	[list of commands]
return

Add this Event sub-routine to your code. You will also need to use the angleTo(x,y) function here.

Set the global variable _a you created to be the returned value from the angleTo(x,y) call.
 
The syntax of this will look like:
let [var] = call angleTo(int x, int y) *where int x and int y are the onTouch sub-routine's parameters

Remember to seperate the program code from the sub-routine method with the END keyword.
</hint>
<answer>let _a = 0
while 1 do
	call bot_move(_a, 5)
loop
end
sub onTouch with x,y
	let _a = call angleTo(x,y)
return
</answer>
</stage>
<stage>
<hint>Goal: Rotate your BOT's turret with the base rotation from the angleTo(x,y) method.

To accomplish this, simply set the angle of the bot_turn(int angle) to be the value you set from the angleTo(x,y) call previously done.
</hint>
<answer>let _a = 0
while 1 do
	call bot_move(_a, 5)
loop
end
sub onTouch with x,y
	let _a = call angleTo(x,y)
	call bot_turn(_a)
return
</answer>
</stage>
</tutorial>