<tutorial>
<title>Declaring Variables</title>
<text>
The first tool you will need on your 
way to programming your bot is declaring 
different types of variables. The following 
Tutorial will do its best to teach you the
basics.

As you already know, the language your bot 
can interpret is BASIC. Therefore, you must
learn the basics of this language for 
maneuvering your bot around, and handling 
interactions. The most basic tool you will
need to learn is declaring, and setting values
to variables. The following is an example of the
simple program you created in the first tutorial
redesigned with the use of declaring and assigning
variables:

Dim s as String
Let s = "hello world"
Print s

The KEYWORD Dim as you can see in the first line above
is used to declare a variable. In this case the variable 
name is "s" and is of TYPE String. The same format holds 
for Integer, Double, etc. 

The second line is where you can see we assigned a value
of the same type as declared in the first line, String.
The keyword LET tells the computer that you are going to 
be assigning a variable a value. Here we Let s = "hello world"
from here until the program ends, the variable s will hold this 
value, or until the user manipulates it.

To get a feel for declaring variables: 

1. declare a variable of type Integer

2. Assign the variable to some number

3. Print the value of the variable to the console.
</text>


<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------- -->
<stage>
<hint>
Goal: Create a variable named 'i' with an Integer data type.

The 'Dim' command is used to declare a variable
	
The syntax of this command is:
Dim [var] as [type]

In this case, replace [var] with 'i' and [type] with 'Integer'

Your code should look like:
Dim i as Integer
</hint>

<answer>Dim i as Integer</answer>
</stage>



<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------- -->
<stage>
<hint>
Goal: Assign an integer value to a variable

The 'Let' command is used to assign values to variables
	
The syntax of this command is:
Let [var] = [value]

In this case, replace [var] with 'i' and [value] with '15'

Your code should look like:
Dim i as Integer
Let i = 15
</hint>

<answer>Dim i as Integer
Let i = 15</answer>
</stage>



<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------- -->
<stage>
<hint>
Goal: Print the value of a variable to the console

The 'Print' command is used to print things on the screen
	
The syntax of this command is:
Print [expression]

In this case, replace [expression] with 'i'

Your code should look like:
Dim i as Integer
Let i = 15
Print i
</hint>

<answer>Dim i as Integer
Let i = 15
Print i</answer>
</stage>


</tutorial>