<tutorial>
<title>Getting Started</title>
<text>Welcome to the Tutorial's section of Bit Bot!
This is not a tutorial. This section is to introduce 
you to the environment you will be using for the other tutorials.
The following text will describe the steps it will take to 
complete the tutorials. 

The tutorial text for all tutorials will be displayed in this 
"Sliding Drawer" where you are reading this now. This is both
open and close-able for a quick reference to the tutorial itself.

There are 4 buttons to make good use of throughout tutorial completions.
These buttons are: Sequence, Selection, Iteration, and Quick Tools.
The Sequence, Selection, and Iteration buttons provide the user with the
shell code for each of these types of programming basics. When clicking on 
one of these buttons a Pop-up menu will show with some of these basic shells.
Selecting one of these will input the shell text into the editing area 
simplifying the coding process on your Android Device. 
The Quick Tools button will similarly Pop-up a menu with some useful buttons
that may be difficult to find on your Devices Keyboard, for example brackets [],
Quotations "", or Braces {}. 

The most important buttons to be aware of on completion of a tutorial 
are the "Lock in Text" and "Simulate" buttons. When a user has entered the 
text believed to be required by the tutorial, they should hit this "Lock in Text"
button. This will verify that their input is in fact correct, or needs modified. 
After verifying your answer is correct, the "Simulate" button will run your code.
** Note however, not all tutorials will use this Simulation button.

To get back to the list of tutorials available for completion, Hit the "Go Back" button.
Or simply hit the back button on your phone.

Feel free to "play" around with the buttons and get a feel for how things will work.

Remember, these tutorials will unlock new "parts" for you Bot, so don't forget
to come back and complete them.
</text>
<answer></answer>
<hint1></hint1>
<hint2></hint2>
<hint3></hint3>
</tutorial>