<Tutorial-Intro>
<stage>
<hint>
Welcome to the Tutorial's section of Bit Bot! 
This section is to introduce you to the environment you will be using for the other tutorials.
The following text will describe the steps it will take to complete the tutorials.
</hint>
</stage>
<stage>
<hint>
The tutorial text for all tutorials will be displayed in the previous screen you were just at. 
The green arrow on this screen will contain hints available to you for the specific tutorial.
This is both open and close-able for a quick reference to the tutorial itself.
</hint>
</stage>
<stage>
<hint>
There are 4 buttons to make good use of throughout tutorial completions.
These buttons are: Sequence, Selection, Iteration, and Quick Tools.
The Sequence, Selection, and Iteration buttons provide the user with the shell code for each of these types of programming basics. When clicking on 
one of these buttons a Pop-up menu will show with some of these basic shells.
Selecting one of these will input the shell text into the editing area simplifying the coding process on your Android Device. 
</hint>
</stage>
<stage>
<hint>
The Quick Tools button will similarly Pop-up a menu with some useful buttons that may be difficult to find on your Devices Keyboard, for example brackets [], Quotations "", or Braces {}. 
</hint>
</stage>
<stage>
<hint>
The most important buttons to be aware of on completion of a tutorial are the buttons with the Lock and Monitor images. When a user has entered the text believed to be required by the tutorial, they should hit this "Lock"
button. This will verify that their input is in fact correct, or needs modified. 
After verifying your answer is correct and all steps to a given tutorial are completed, the "Simulate" button will run your code.
** Note however, not all tutorials will use this Simulation button.
</hint>
</stage>
<stage>
<hint>
Remember, these tutorials will unlock new "parts" for you Bot, so don't forget to come back and complete them.
</hint>
</stage>
</Tutorial-Intro>